Guide to the Regional Science Association International records, 1964-2017.
Regional Science Association International records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Regional Science Association International records, 1964-2017.
4991
Regional Science Association International.
18.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, conference meeting files, papers delivered, annual meeting records, subject files.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Formerly the Regional Science Association. Academic and professional individuals concerned with practice and advancement of urban and regional analysis and related studies.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, conference meeting files, papers delivered, annual meeting records, subject files pertaining to North American meetings, Summer Institute and workshop files, Council minutes, RSA Newsletters, proposals, research and editorial files, audiotapes, publications, and other records of the organization; includes personal correspondence and working files of David E. Boyce, conference coordinator and program chair of North American meetings.
Includes material related to organizing the 1976 North American Annual Meeting of the Regional Science Association
SUBJECTS
Names:
Regional Science Association International.; Boyce, David E.; Regional Science Association.
Subjects:
Regional planning--Study and teaching
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- World Congresses, 1980 (Box 1)
- Council Meetings and Conferences, 1980 (Box 2)
- Various Conference Admin. Detail, Date Unknown (Box 3)
- World Congresses and Conferences, 1980-1989 (Box 4)
- Files on International Section, Date Unknown (Box 5)
- Minutes of Meetings, Various Admin. Files and RSA Newsletter, Date Unknown (Box 6)
- Applications to National Science Foundation and Proposal for Walter Isard's Honorary Degree, Date Unknown (Box 7)
- RSA Reorganization Proposal, Date Unknown (Box 8)
- Manographs, Journal Paper and Graduate Course Detail, Date Unknown (Box 9)
- NSF Proposals and Files Relating to Publication, Date Unknown (Box 10)
- Paper Drafts, Date Unknown (Box 11)
- Regional Science Research Institute Discussion Paper Series, 1964-1972 (Box 12)
- Regional Science Research Institute Discussion Paper Series, 1973-1980 (Box 13)
- RSAI Urbana office, 1982-2013 (Box 15)
  Includes H. Kohno's manuscript for History of Japan section and David Boyce's personal files
- RSA conference materials and publications, 1963-2017 (Box 16)
  Includes some other conferences
- XXXVIIeme colloque de l'ASRDLF - La Science Regionale au Tournant du Siecle, 2001-09; CD-4937; Association de Science Regionale de Langue Francaise (Box 16)
- 38th European Congress, Vienna, 1998-08; CD-4938; Regional Science Association (Box 16)
- Papers in Regional Sciences - Volumes 1-83.1 - 1955-2004, 2004; CD-4941; Regional Science Association International (Box 16)
- 51st North American Meeting, Seattle - Abstracts, 2004-11; CD-4942; Regional Science Association International (Box 16)
- RSAI Membership Database and Program - DBF format, 2004-12; CD-4943; Coal, Joan (Box 16)
- 54th Annual North American Meeting, Savannah - Abstracts, authors, program, 2007-11; CD-4944; Regional Science Association International (Box 16)
- 6th World Congress of the RSAI, Lugano, 2000-05; CD-4945; Regional Science Association International (Box 16)
- ERSA 2002 - From Industry to Advanced Services - Perspectives of European Metropolitan Regions - Congress CD-ROM, 2002; CD-4946; European Regional Science Association (Box 16)
- 43rd Congress of the European Regional Science Association, 2003-08; CD-4947; European Regional Science Association (Box 16)
- Newsletters, 1951-2017 (Box 17)
- History of Regional Science I, Undated; FD-925; Isard, Walter (Box 17)
- PRSCO, WRSA, NARSC, RSA Council, 1985-2008 (Box 18)
- NARSC, conference proceedings, W. Beyer's notebook, 1964-2001 (Box 19)
  Includes W. Beyer's 1964 notebook from the Berkeley Regional Science Workshop, documents related to the NARSC constitution, and conference proceedings from Korea, Japan, Germany, and the US.
- The Daily Pennsylvanian, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  Issues of The Daily Pennsylvanian documenting the closure of the RS department at Upenn.
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Books - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Regional Studies in Poland: Experiences and Prospects /[edited by Antoni Kuklinski]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 1986.
Changes in the Regional Economy in the Period of System Transformation /[edited by Ryszard Domanski and Eamonn Judge]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 1994.
Towards the Explanation and Modelling of the Spatial and Regional Dimensions of the Transformation Process /[edited by Ryszard Domanski]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 1996.
The Spatial Transformation of the Economy /[edited by Ryszard Domanski]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 1998.
Emerging Spatial and Regional Structures of an Economy in Transition /[edited by Ryszard Domanski]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 1998.
The Competitiveness of Regions in the Polish and European Perspective /[edited by Ryszard Domanski]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 1999.
Cities and Regions in an Englarging European Union /[edited by Ryszard Domanski]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 2002.
Polycentric Metropolitan Regions - New Concepts and Experiences /[edited by Tadeusz Markowski and Tadeusz Marszal]. - [Poland]: Polish Academy of Sciences Committee for Space Economy and Regional Planning, 2002.
Recent Developments in Regional Science /[edited by Rolf Funck]. 1972.
Studies in Regional Science /[edited by Allen J. Scott]. 1969.
Urban and Regional Planning /[edited by A.G. Wilson]. 1971.
Regional Development and Planning: International Perspectives /[edited by Antoni Kuklinski]. 1975.
Space-Structure-Economy: A Tribute to August Losch /[edited by Rolf Funck and Antoni Kuklinski]. 1986.